Welcome to the iOS Lead Essentials
歡迎來到 iOS Lead Essentials
program
課程
we're so excited to have you with us and
我們很高興你能加入我們，並且
you may be excited to join as well
你也可能對此感到興奮
hopefully or you may be wondering if you
希望如此，或者你可能在想你是否
made
做了
the right choice what I want to say for
正確的選擇，我想確定說的是
sure
確定的是
is that this program works you will see
這個課程是有效的，你將會看見並且
and interact with
互動與
lead iOS developers working in exciting
在激動人心的應用程式和公司工作的 iOS 主程式設計師
apps and companies
所以，見證他們的成功會激勵你
so seeing their success will inspire you
也去達成
to get there
因此別忘了打個招呼並且
too so don't forget to say hi and
自我介紹
present yourself
在 Slack 社群上
in the Slack community exactly
確實如此
in our community there are bootcamp and
在我們的社群裡有訓練營和
university graduates
大學畢業生
self-taught developers, juniors, mid-level
自學成才的開發者，初級、中階
seniors, lead developers so
資深、主程式設計師，所以
regardless your current level there is
無論你現在的水平如何，這裡都有
space for you to thrive in the program
你在課程中蓬勃發展的空間
definitely so before you jump right in
無疑的是，在你真正投入
the lectures
講座之前
we'd like to get you ready for what's to
我們希望讓你為接下來的事情做好準備
come so this dev program is designed to
所以這個開發者計劃是為了提升你的
get your dev skills
開發技巧
to the next level your goal in this
把它提升到下一個等級你在這個
program is to achieve
計劃中的目標是
technical excellence as an iOS developer
成為技術卓越的 iOS 開發者
and position yourself as a leader
並將自己定位為行業的領導者
in the software industry so there are
在軟件行業中所以這裡有
over 60 lectures
超過60堂課
here plus mentoring sessions and live
還有邊袖指導和現場
sessions
會議
lots and lots of detail but just like
內容非常詳細但就像
you don't learn
你不能僅靠看視頻學會
to ride a bike by watching videos you
騎自行車一樣，看視頻也無法
don't master software development
掌握軟件開發
by watching videos you master it by
看視頻無法使你掌握它，你需要
doing it
去做才行
exactly and this program is all about
對，這個計劃就是要讓
getting you doing the right things
你去做正確的事情
hundreds of developers have taken this
數百個開發者參加了此
course because it works
課程因為它確實有效
but you need to do the work so just
但你需要去做這些工作所以僅僅
watching a lecture and watching it with
看一堂課並且專注地
intention
看這堂課。
is 100% different it's a completely
是100%不同的，是完全
different thing
不同的東西
so do it with the intention to learn
所以要帶著學習的態度去做
take notes and practice
作筆記並加以實踐
so you need to complete all lectures
所以你需要完成所有的講座
all of them all of them and it is your
全部，都要全部, 這是你的
practice
實踐
so follow the instructions and complete
所以跟著指示，完成
all challenges as well
所有的挑戰
Mike and I will review all your
Mike和我將審查你所有的
challenges one by one
挑戰一個接一個
and will provide feedback to you exactly
並且將對你完成每一節講座時
and every time you complete a lecture
提供反饋
don't forget to press
不要忘記按
the complete button and also to submit
完成按鈕，並把你的解決方案提交到GitHub
your challenge solutions to GitHub
如果你按序完成講座
exactly if you complete the lectures in
order
按順序
and you solve the challenges you will
並解決挑戰，你將會
get invited to mentoring sessions with
被邀請參加我們的指導環節
us
與我們一起
we are here to help you but we cannot do
我們在這裡幫助你，但無法替你
the work for you
完成工作
so if you do the work you get the
所以如果你完成工作，你將會
results
獲得結果
exactly and of course during the
確實的，在課程的
lectures a lot of questions will come up
在聽講座時將會產生許多問題
so you need to ask questions about the
因此您需要提出關於
lectures that's how you're gonna get the
講座的問題，這樣您才能從中
most
獲得
of this program you need to interact
最多的收益，您需要與我們互動
with us because we're here to help you
因為我們在這裡就是要幫助您
so you'll find guidelines to ask
所以您會找到提問的
questions to ask good questions
指南，以提出好的問題
so don't skip this section you need to
所以不要跳過這部分，您需要
go one by one and you need to read it
一步步來，並且需要閱讀它
exactly one by one in order
按照順序一步步來
so you get the most of this program
這樣您才能從這個程序中獲得最多的收益
you'll also learn
您還會學習到
from answers to thousands of questions
來自數千個問題的答案
from the students
來自學生的
you have access to all of them so you'll
您可以查看所有的，因此您會
see how people
看到其他人
like you are leveling up for example
就像您一樣正在進步，例如
let's search for Core Data we have
我們搜尋Core Data，我們有
lectures about Core Data
關於Core Data的講座
and there are threads and threads and
並且還有關於Core Data的
threads about Core Data
討論串和討論串，以及討論串
from other students from questions
來自其他學生的問題
that's it so you can find here by
就是這樣，所以你可以在這裡找到
keyword
關鍵字
the topics you want to learn about but
你想學習的主題，但是
you need to follow the lectures in order
你需要按照順序跟著講座才行
you need to complete
你需要完成
all of them yes so your next step
所有這些，所以你的下一步
is to read all the information in the
是閱讀在
Start here module
開始這裡模組的所有信息
in this first section read all of them
在這第一部分閱讀所有的
in order to make the most
為了充分利用
of this program and of course we're here
這個程序，並且我們在這裡
to help
幫助你
but you need to do the work we cannot do
但是你需要去做這些工作，我們不能替你做
the work for you
不能做你需要做的工作
no so that's it it starts now
不，所以就是這樣，現在開始
keep doing the work go through the
繼續做這些工作，依次通過
lectures one by one
講座
complete them practice take notes ask
完成它們，練習，做筆記，提問
questions
問問題
and we are here to help that's it we'll
我們在這裡幫助你，就是這樣，我們會
see you
見你
in the next lecture see ya
在下次講座，再見